linkskat.com 2019-06-27

# Privacy Policy - LinksKat

Information Collection  
Information Usage  
Information Protection   
Cookie Usage   
3rd Party Disclosure  
3rd Party Links  
Google AdSense  

Our Contact Information This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.   
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?   
We do not collect information from visitors of our site. or other details to help you with your experience.   
When do we collect information?   
We collect information from you when you or enter information on our site.   
Contact us form   
How do we use your information?   
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:   
• To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)   
How do we protect visitor information?   
We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.   
We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information like email addresses or credit card numbers.   
We do not use Malware Scanning.   
We do not use an SSL certificate   
• We do not need an SSL because:  
Do we use 'cookies'?  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:  
• Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.  
• Keep track of advertisements.   
• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.  
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.   
If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.  
However, you can still place orders .  
Third-party disclosure We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.   
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.   
Third-party links  
We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.   
Google  
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.  
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.  
We have implemented the following:   
• Remarketing with Google AdSense  
• Google Display Network Impression Reporting  
• Demographics and Interests Reporting  
• DoubleClick Platform Integration  
We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.  
Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.   
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)  
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.  
We do not specifically market to children under 13.  
CAN SPAM Act  
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.  
We collect your email address in order to:  
To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:   
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.  
Contacting Us  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  
LinksKat.com  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
Last Edited on 2018-04-3
